REBECCA NGUYEN, CPA

(713) 391-6757 | rtanguyen@gmail.com | Austin, TX

SUMMARY

Self-driven full stack developer with experience in building and implementing web-based applications. Adept at working independently as well as collaborating with teams across multiple functions in a deadline intensive environment. Dedicated to learning, evaluating, and applying new technologies in order to enhance functionality, usability, and efficiency.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript (including ES6), SQL, Visual Basic Libraries & Frameworks: Node.js, ReactJS, Express, JQuery, Bootstrap, Webpack Databases: MongoDB, Mongoose, MySQL, Sequelize

PROJECTS

Movie Mixer: Web application to recommend movies and drinks based on user selection of genre and spirit

- GitHub: https://github.com/rtanguyen/MovieMixer
- Deployed: https://rtanguyen.github.io/MovieMixer/
- Built With: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, Bulma

Miso Hungry: Web application to browse, review, and favorite recipes

- GitHub: https://github.com/rtanguyen/miso-hungry
- Deployed: https://intense-temple-14332.herokuapp.com/
- Built With: JavaScript, Node.js, Express, MySQL, Sequelize, Handlebars, CSS

EXPERIENCE

Tax Senior, Deloitte | Houston, TX

SEPTEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2021

- Incorporated data analytics tools to increase efficiency in compliance projects and allow teams to effectively assist clients with tax planning effort
- Responsible for overseeing daily tasks throughout completion of engagements. Included supervising and delegating assignments to staff, coordinating with internal teams and maintaining client relations

Tax Consultant, Deloitte | Houston, TX

MAY 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2019

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development

THE UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AT AUSTIN | 2021

Master of Science in Accountancy

THE UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON, C.T. BAUER COLLEGE OF BUSINESS | HOUSTON, TX | 2016 - 2017

Bachelor of Business Administration, Accounting

THE UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON, C.T. BAUER COLLEGE OF BUSINESS | HOUSTON, TX | 2011 - 2015